&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：在这个提升练习中，你将有机会
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: In this hoisting exercise, you're gonna get a chance to
实践这个想法，将函数带出它们的作用域，如果它们
practice with that idea of bringing functions out of their scopes if they
不需要嵌套，也不需要使用作用域底部的函数。
don't need to be nested, or using functions at the bottom of scopes.
就像我们刚才在讲座中谈到的那样，
That sort of thing like we've just talked about in the lecture,
你会有机会练习的。
you're gonna get a chance to practice with that.
所以我们将采用已经使用各种功能的现有代码库
So we're gonna take an existing code base that already uses a variety of function
表达式，我们将使用新发现的
expressions, and we're going to refactor that code base using our newfound
提升的知识，我们改变书写方式的能力。
knowledge of hoisting, our ability to change the way that it's written.
我们没有改变任何行为，我们只是简单地改变了编码风格。
We're not changing any behavior, we're just simply changing the coding style.
如果你看它的当前版本，它看起来是这样的。
If you look at the current version of it, It looks like this.
我们有一组函数声明和内联函数表达式，
We have a set of function declarations and inline function expressions,
在几个地方我们可以使用内联函数表达式
and there are several places where we have inline function expressions
其实并不需要是内联函数表达式。
that don't really need to be inline function expressions.
一次这样的例子，就在这里。
Once such example, right here.
该函数表达式没有使用其自身周围的任何词法变量，所以
That function expression isn't using any of the lexical variables around itself, so
没有特别的理由内联它，除了可能只是一种风格偏好。
there's no particular reason to inline it, other than maybe just a style preference.
但是没有机械的理由这样做。
But there's no mechanical reason to do so.
所以利用我们所知道的函数声明和
So using what we know about function declarations and
函数提升，让我们把那个拉出来。
function hoisting, let's pull that one out.
所以你在寻找
So you look for
可以将函数拉出到外部范围的那些示例，
those examples where functions can be pulled out to an outer scope,
如果它们不需要嵌套，那么就会使作用域结构更简单、更平坦。
if they don't need to be nested, that makes simpler and flatter scope structure.
你的作用域结构越简单越平坦，
And the simpler and flatter the scope structure you have,
就越容易阅读和理解。
the easier it will be to read and understand.
它越嵌套，就越难跟踪所有这些边界。
The more nested it is, the harder it is to keep track of all those boundaries.
此外，您会注意到所有可执行代码都在底部
Also, you'll notice that all the executable code is at the bottom
这个程序。
of this program.
我们学到的关于函数提升的内容是，我们可以将可执行文件
And what we learned about function hoisting is that we can put executable
代码在顶部，所有函数在底部。
code at the top, and all the functions at the bottom.
所以你的任务是对这些函数进行重构或重新安排，
So your task is to sort of refactor, or rearrange, these functions,
在需要的地方将它们拉出来，并重构此代码，使之
pull them out where necessary, And refactor this code so
它使用或利用函数提升的好处。
that it uses or leverages the benefits of function hoisting.